Guide to the Dorothy Porter Wesley Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Series IV. Personal Papers
  - General Personal Papers of Dorothy Porter Welsey
    - Addresses and Business Cards, Circa 1935-1995 (Box 284, Folder 2606-2611)
    - Addresses and Business Cards, Circa 1935-1995 (Box 285, Folder 2612-2615)
    - Affidavit, 1977- (Box 285, Folder 2616)
    - Alpha Stationary, Circa 1981 (Box 285, Folder 2617)
    - Awards, Honors and Certificates, 1957-1998 (Box 285, Folder 2618-2622)
    - Awards, Honors and Certificates, 1957-1998 (Box 286, Folder 2623-2629)
    - Awards, Honors and Certificates, 1957-1998 (Box 287, Folder 2630-2637)
    - Awards, Honors and Certificates, 1957-1998 (Box 288, Folder 2638)
    - Awards, Honors and Certificates, 1959-1979 (Box 338 (Oversize), Folder 3029-3030)
    - Awards, Honors and Certificates, 1983-1989 (Box 339 (Oversize), Folder 3031-3032)
    - Awards, Honors and Certificates, 1993- (Box 340 (Oversize), Folder 3033-3034)
    - Blank application forms, Cica 1973-1991 (Box 288, Folder 2639)
    - Blank Postcards, Circa 1906-1995 (Box 288, Folder 2640-2641)
    - Blank stationery, Undated (Box 288, Folder 2642-2643)
    - Calendars, 1962-1995 (Box 289, Folder 2644-2649)
    - Calendars, 1990- (Box 341 (Oversize), Folder 3035 (Oversize))
    - California Afro-American Museum, deed of gift, 1985-1986 (Box 290, Folder 2650)
    - Christmas List, 1965- (Box 290, Folder 2651)
    - Codicil to the Porter Wesley Family Trust, 1988-1994 (Box 290, Folder 2652)
    - Dedication and Naming of Church Library, 1993- (Box 290, Folder 2653)
    - Dorothy Porter Wesley's death, memorial service and obituaries, 1995-1996 (Box 290, Folder 2654-2658)
    - Oversize, 1995- (Box 341 (Oversize), Folder 3036)
    - Driver's liscence and passports, 1935-1989 (Box 290, Folder 2659-2660)
    - France Trip, 1935- (Box 291, Folder 2661)
    - France Trip, Undated (Box 341 (Oversize), Folder 3037)
    - Funeral programs and obituaries of others, 1914-1996 (Box 291, Folder 2662)
    - Geneaology of Burnett and Ball Families, Undated (Box 291, Folder 2663)
    - Geneaology of Murray Family, Undated (Box 291, Folder 2664)
    - Gettysburg Address, 1863 (copy), Undated (Box 341 (Oversize), Folder 3038)
    - Guestbooks, 1962-1973 (Box 291, Folder 2665-2666)
    - Hymns, Circa 1906 (Box 291, Folder 2667)
    - Jury Duty, 1990-1995 (Box 291, Folder 2668)
    - Marriage Certificate and bridal book of James Amos Porter and Dorothy Burnett Porter, 1929- (Box 291, Folder 2669)
    - Marriage Certificate of Charles Harris Wesley and Dorothy Porter Wesley, 1979- (Box 291, Folder 2670)
    - May Sullivan, power of attorney, 1992- (Box 292, Folder 2671)
    - Medical files, 1994- (Box 292, Folder 2672)
    - Museum of the National Center of Afro-American Artists, loan agreement, 1973- (Box 292, Folder 2673)
    - Reccomendations, 1974-1990 (Box 292, Folder 2674)
    - Reminiscenes (notes), Undated (Box 292, Folder 2675)
    - Resumes of others, Circa 1969-1984 (Box 292, Folder 2676)
    - Ribbons, Undated (Box 292, Folder 2677)
    - Schomburg Center for Research in Black Culture, deed of gift, 1990- (Box 292, Folder 2678)
    - Student Papers, 1969- (Box 292, Folder 2679)
    - Shew Fly! Arranged by Rollin Howard, 1869- (Box 341 (Oversize), Folder 3039)
    - Scrapbook materials and clippings, Circa 1935-1994 (Box 292, Folder 2680)
    - Scrapbook materials and clippings, Circa 1935-1994 (Box 341 (Oversize), Folder 3040)
    - Table Graces, Undated (Box 293, Folder 2681)
    - Transcripts and report cards, 1918-1952 (Box 293, Folder 2682)
    - Trip ephemera and travel diary, Circa 1920-1935 (Box 293, Folder 2683)
    - Visa Applications, 1963- (Box 293, Folder 2684)
    - Wilson-Greene's Concert, 1928-1929 (Box 293, Folder 2685)
    - Yearbooks, 1929-1956 (Box 293, Folder 2686-2688)
    - Yearbooks, 1960- (Box 294, Folder 2689)
    - Notebooks, Circa 1942-1989 (Box 294, Folder 2690)
    - Clippings collected by Dorothy Porter Wesley, 1918-1995 (Box 295, Folder 2691-2696)
    - Clippings collected by Dorothy Porter Wesley, Circa 1925-1996 (Box 342 (Oversize), Folder 3049-3054)
    - Clippings collected by Dorothy Porter Wesley, circa 1925-1976 (Box 342a (Oversize), Folder 3054a-3054f)
  - Financial Records
    - Airline Expenses, 1962-1990 (Box 296, Folder 2697-2700)
    - Auto expenses and gasoline, 1977-1978 (Box 296, Folder 2701)
    - Bank Statements, Circa 1963-1991 (Box 296, Folder 2702-2703)
    - Bank Statements, Circa 1963-1991 (Box 297, Folder 2704-2708)
    - Bank Statements, Circa 1963-1991 (Box 298, Folder 2709-2715)
    - Bank Statements, Circa 1963-1991 (Box 299, Folder 2716)
    - Bills and Receipts, Circa 1943-1998 (Box 299, Folder 2717-2720)
    - Bills and Receipts, Circa 1943-1998 (Box 300, Folder 2721-2727)
    - Bills and Receipts, Circa 1943-1998 (Box 301, Folder 2728-2733)
    - Bills and Receipts, Circa 1943-1998 (Box 302, Folder 2734)
    - Canceled checkbooks, 1968-1978 (Box 302, Folder 2735)
    - Checks and receipts, 1966-1991 (Box 302, Folder 2736-2740)
    - Checks and receipts, 1966-1991 (Box 303, Folder 2741-2747)
    - Checks and receipts, 1966-1991 (Box 304, Folder 2748-2754)
    - Checks and receipts, 1966-1991 (Box 305, Folder 2755)
    - Closed Accounts, 1975-1988 (Box 305, Folder 2756-2757)
    - Contributions, 1987- (Box 305, Folder 2758)
    - Deed of trust, 1977-1978 (Box 305, Folder 2759)
    - Deposit Books, 1957-1967 (Box 305, Folder 2760)
    - Event tickets, 1992- (Box 305, Folder 2761)
    - Falmouth lot, 1970-1985 (Box 305, Folder 2762)
    - Gifts, 1972-1973 (Box 305, Folder 2763)
    - Harriet Lane taxes, 1967-1970 (Box 305, Folder 2764)
    - Howard University Credit Union, 1948-1966 (Box 305, Folder 2765)
    - Howard University payslips, 1967-1989 (Box 306, Folder 2766-2767)
    - Income tax returns and receipts, 1975-1992 (Box 306, Folder 2768-2776)
    - Income tax returns and receipts, 1975-1992 (Box 307, Folder 2777-2780)
    - Insurance, 1960-1991 (Box 307, Folder 2781)
    - Medical expenses, 1991-1992 (Box 307, Folder 2782)
    - Oyster Harbor bills and receipts, 1950-1956 (Box 307, Folder 2783-2784)
    - Receipts, 1963-1996 (Box 308, Folder 2785-2792)
    - Receipts, 1963-1996 (Box 309, Folder 2793-2795)
    - Receipts, 1963-1996 (Box 310, Folder 2796-2801)
    - Receipts for art, 1960-1961 (Box 310, Folder 2802)
    - Royalties, 1971-1977 (Box 311, Folder 2803)
    - Single Family Home Sales, 1996- (Box 311, Folder 2804)
    - Snider House bills and receipts, 1969- (Box 311, Folder 2805)
    - Stocks, 1977- (Box 311, Folder 2806)
    - Supreme Life Insurance, 1991- (Box 311, Folder 2807)
    - Notes, Circa 1960-1998 (Box 311, Folder 2808-2809)
  - Photographs
    - Portraits, Circa 1941-1995 (Box 311, Folder 2810-2811)
    - Portraits, Circa 1941-1995 (Box 312, Folder 2812-2824)
    - Portraits, Circa 1941 (Box 343 (Oversize), Folder 3055-3056)
    - Friends and Family, Circa 1920-1995 (Box 312, Folder 2825)
    - Friends and Family, Circa 1920-1995 (Box 313, Folder 2826-2835)
    - Friends and Family, Circa 1920-1995 (Box 314, Folder 2836-2841)
    - Photogravure, Undated (Box 314, Folder 2842)
    - Places, Circa 1930-1969 (Box 314, Folder 2843-2845)
    - Places, Circa 1930-1969 (Box 315, Folder 2846-2855)
    - Work, Circa 1940-1997 (Box 315, Folder 2856-2859)
    - Work, Circa 1940-1997 (Box 316, Folder 2860-2868)
    - Work, Circa 1940-1997 (Box 317, Folder 2869-2872)
    - Negatives and slides, Circa 1961 (Box 317, Folder 2873-2874)
  - Ephemera
    - Book covers (Box 318, Folder 2875)
    - Bookmarks (Box 318, Folder 2876)
    - Brochures and programs, 1935-1995 (Box 318, Folder 2877-2882)
    - Brochures and programs, 1935-1995 (Box 319, Folder 2883-2888)
    - Brochures and programs, 1935-1995 (Box 320, Folder 2889-2894)
    - Brochures and programs, 1935-1995 (Box 321, Folder 2895-2901)
    - Brochures and programs, 1935-1995 (Box 322, Folder 2902-2903)
    - Brochures and Programs, 1965- (Box 341 (Oversize), Folder 3041)
    - Cardboard and matchbook, Undated (Box 322, Folder 2904)
    - Jewelry, Undated (Box 322, Folder 2905)
    - Magazines, 1927-2002 (Box 322, Folder 2906-2908)
    - Magazines, 1927-2002 (Box 323, Folder 2909-2915)
    - Magazines, 1927-2002 (Box 324, Folder 2916-2921)
    - Magazines, 1927-2002 (Box 325, Folder 2922)
    - Magazines, 1974-1994 (Box 341 (Oversize), Folder 3042-3043)
    - Maps, Undated (Box 325, Folder 2923)
    - Newsletters, 1963-1996 (Box 325, Folder 2924-2929)
    - Newsletters, 1963-1996 (Box 326, Folder 2930-2936)
    - Newsletters, 1963-1996 (Box 327, Folder 2937)
    - Parking permits and stickers, 1972-1973 (Box 327, Folder 2938)
    - Stamps, Undated (Box 327, Folder 2939)
  - Family Papers
    - Constance Porter Uzelac (1939-2012)
      - Art Noir, Circa 1995-2000 (Box 327, Folder 2940-2945)
      - Art Noir, Circa 1995-2000 (Box 328, Folder 2946-2947)
      - Art Noir, 1995- (Box 341 (Oversize), Folder 3044)
      - The Bondwoman's Narrative, Rebuttal (Copy), 2001- (Box 328, Folder 2948-2951)
      - Broward County Library, 2000-2003 (Box 328, Folder 2952-2953)
      - Court documents, 1990- (Box 329, Folder 2956)
      - Drawings, Circa 1943-1944 (Box 329, Folder 2957)
      - Exhibition Sketches, Circa 1990 (Box 329, Folder 2958)
      - James Amos Porter Colloquium Series, Circa 1992-1995 (Box 329, Folder 2959)
      - Oversize, 1995- (Box 341 (Oversize), Folder 3045)
      - James Amos Porter papers (loan documents), Circa 1998-2006 (Box 329, Folder 2960)
      - Receipts, 2003- (Box 329, Folder 2961)
      - Social Security card and Marriage Certificate, 1964- (Box 329, Folder 2962)
      - Clippings collected by Constance Porter Uzelac, Circa 1937-2002 (Box 329, Folder 2963)
      - Clippings collected by Constance Porter Uzelac, Circa 1937-2002 (Box 341 (Oversize), Folder 3046)
      - Clippings collected by Constance Porter Uzelac, 2003- (Box 344 (Oversize), Folder 3057-3058)
    - James Amos Porter (1905-1970)
      - Art Book Research, 1941-1969 (Box 329, Folder 2964)
      - Death Certificate, obituaries and estate, 1970-1971 (Box 328, Folder 2954-2955)
    - Charles Harris Wesley (1891-1987)
      - Memorial Services, 1987- (Box 329, Folder 2965)
    - Roberta (Bertha) Ball Burnett Sadler (1887-1961)
      - Autobiography, 1959- (Box 329, Folder 2966)
      - Bills and receipts, 1956- (Box 330, Folder 2967)
      - Death Certificates, grave deed and funeral expenses, 1942-1961 (Box 330, Folder 2968)
      - St. Marks Methodist Chruch, Play, Circa 1940 (Box 330, Folder 2969)
      - Tennis records, 1927-1937 (Box 330, Folder 2970)
      - Clippings and ephemera, 1937-1960 (Box 330, Folder 2971)
      - Clippings and ephemera, 1960- (Box 341 (Oversize), Folder 3047)
      - Notebook, 1950- (Box 330, Folder 2972)
    - Hayes Joseph Burnett (1877-1922)
      - Certificates and Clippings, 1902-1923 (Box 330, Folder 2973)
      - Hair Perscription, Circa 1900-1922 (Box 330, Folder 2974)
      - Howard University Medical Department commencement 1903-1904 and The National Medical Association magazine, 1903-1910 (Box 330, Folder 2975)
    - Hayes Joseph Burnett II (1905-1955)
      - Clippings and photographs, 1948-1987 (Box 330, Folder 2976)
      - Lincoln University commencement books, 1928-1929 (Box 331, Folder 2977)
    - George W. Burnett
      - Clippings and Buffalo Soldier papers, 1937-1991 (Box 331, Folder 2978)
  - Leonie Burnett Harper (1906-1992)
    - Awards, honors, and certificates, 1957-1985 (Box 331, Folder 2979)
    - Bills and receipts, 1984- (Box 331, Folder 2980)
    - Driver's permit and passport, Circa 1960-1963 (Box 331, Folder 2981)
    - Harper Family Trust, 1914-1994 (Box 331, Folder 2982-2983)
    - Memorial service, program, and obituary, 1992- (Box 331, Folder 2984)
  - Alice Taylor
    - Certificates, job applications and clippings, 1930-1978 (Box 331, Folder 2985)
    - Recipes, Undated (Box 332, Folder 2986)
    - Notes, Undated (Box 332, Folder 2987-2988)
    - Mary Louisiana Burnett Artis
      - Contracts, will and ephemera, 1908-1943 (Box 332, Folder 2989)
  - Lula and Bertha Allan Papers
    - Lula Allan (1879-1968)
      - Correspondence, Circa 1926-1957 (Box 332, Folder 2990-2992)
      - Correspondence, Circa 1926-1957 (Box 333, Folder 2993-2999)
      - Address Books, Undated (Box 333, Folder 3000)
      - Address Books, Undated (Box 334, Folder 3001-3002)
      - Bible (oversize), 1956- (Box 345)
      - Death certificate, obituaries and memorial, 1968- (Box 334, Folder 3003)
      - Death certificate, obituaries, and memorial, 1968- (Box 341 (Oversize), Folder 3048)
      - Estate papers, 1929-1973 (Box 334, Folder 3004-3005)
      - Estate papers, 1929-1973 (Box 335, Folder 3006-3007)
      - Financial Documents, 1936-1970 (Box 335, Folder 3008-3010)
      - Financial Documents, 1936-1970 (Box 336, Folder 3011)
      - Miner Teachers College, 1922-1952 (Box 336, Folder 3012)
      - Photographs, Circa 1900-1973 (Box 336, Folder 3013-3014)
      - Writings collected by Lula Allan, 1905- (Box 336, Folder 3015)
      - Notes, Undated (Box 336, Folder 3016)
    - Bertha Allan (1883-1971)
      - Correspondence, 1912-1970 (Box 336, Folder 3017-3019)
      - Death Certificate, 1971- (Box 337, Folder 3020)
      - Ephemera, 1929-1964 (Box 337, Folder 3021)
      - Estate and lot, 1929-1963 (Box 337, Folder 3022)
      - Financial Documents, 1922-1969 (Box 337, Folder 3023-3026)
      - Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, 1937-1971 (Box 337, Folder 3027)
      - Power of Attorney, 1971- (Box 337, Folder 3028)